[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "You guys want to step in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "Identify yourselves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "I'm Betty.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "Three generations of family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "So what was it like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "It made you appreciate hot water, flushing toilets, electricity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBD", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "But you came through it as a family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "NIDENTIFIED FEMALE: We did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "Were you worried at any point it might not end this way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Yes, the first night was rough because we were tilting very badly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "The ship was listing, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "Yes, very badly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "And what was it like for you guys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "For me, it was really scary because it's never happened to me, and it's my first cruise.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Good to have your mom and grand mom and everybody with you, so you were safe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["June"], "LOCATION": ["Alaska"]}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "So, are you going to go on a cruise again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I actually have one booked in June for Alaska.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "How do you past the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "I had packed some cards.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Are you, and are you going to sue them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "I feel like they didn't start off right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Did you think they kept you informed, and do you feel you were constantly given the right information?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "It was constantly changing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "VBN", ",", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "NN", "MD", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Are they safe and sound if they're feeling OK or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, I think the most important thing is definitely get to a warm shower, a nice bed, and get some rest, because honestly, time will tell what we're going to see in the next couple days from this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "This is Rusty, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Yes, sir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "Excited to be on land.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Do you think you realized because of this and because of what happened, maybe if it was a regular cruise you might not feel this way, and now you appreciate them in a way you didn't?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "IN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Your mom and dad, what was it like to see her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Oh, my word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Where are you headed now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "To the hotel to eat, I hope.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "This was your surprise 40th birthday party?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Yes, it was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What did you have for food?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "They fed us lots of food.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Which would you prefer, a shower or a toilet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, and they got the toilets working today, so we have been using those but probably a hot shower is probably what our pro priority is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "So how was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "It was kind of crazy, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kansas City", "Topeka"]}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "AVIDGE: And where are they right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "They're back in Kansas City, in Topeka.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "I mean, how is it we see you and other still people waiting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "RB", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "He's a platinum member.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "And what has it been like just in the past few hours here waiting to finally finish this ordeal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "It's -- well, today, the mood kind of turned negative, as everyone started listening to what was happening onshore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "You know, just tell us about -- was that a cathartic type of thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", ":", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Yes, tweets are just cathartic to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "You actually have a coat and are not freezing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I have a sweater on right now, but I brought about five books and eight magazines and we have read them al cover to cover.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Did that happen for you also?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "What was the -- if there's a moment, you talk about what was the worst single thing that happened and maybe the best single thing that happened to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", ":", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Well, the worst was -- I'm going to have to say the fire.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Well, get on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Glad to be on land, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Orleans", "South Carolina"]}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "To get on the bus to go to New Orleans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "New Orleans, and then fly out tomorrow to South Carolina.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Orleans"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "That we're almost home?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "LOVE: When we could see land.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "And not to say you're the trouble maker, but this did not go in any way that this family thought, did it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "No, but it was 2 1/2 days of great fun, and then the rest of the time, it was family coming together, bonding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Did you really feel the rough seas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "At times, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "And how do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "Grounded.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Has it finally sunk in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "No, when we were standing at the doors, I said, it still doesn't seem like it's happening.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "What do you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "Pray.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "Did you meet new people through that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Yes, yes, we did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "What happens after the sun goes down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "It was creepy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "So will you ever go again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "Probably not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "How do you get that out of your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "I probably won't, but I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "Are you friends or dating?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "We're friends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 762, "question": "How did you spend the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 763, "answer": "A lot of cards were played.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "Was it there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "The first day, we slept at 6:00.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 794, "question": "You think everyone got along well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 795, "answer": "Not everybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "Was there an organization to the day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "We tried to sleep a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 814, "question": "Are you going to save the robe?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 815, "answer": "I am.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]